[
    {
        "Question":"what was the hqla in the q4 of Citigroup in 2015",
        "Answer":"378.5 billion dollars",
        "Level":"6"
    },
    {
        "Question":"as a result of the sales of certain non-core towers and other assets what was the recorded net losses of American Tower in 2008",
        "Answer":"10.5 million dollars",
        "Level":"6"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what was the port call costsin of Royal Caribbean Cruises in 2012",
        "Answer":"459.8 million dollars",
        "Level":"6"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what is the aggregate rent expense of American Tower Corp in 2014?",
        "Answer":"655.0 million dollars",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what is the long-term component of BlackRock at 12\/31\/2011?",
        "Answer":"593356 million dollars",
        "Level":"6"
    },
    {
        "Question":"at december 31 , 2012 of The PNC Financial Services, what was the potential maximum exposure under the loss share arrangements?",
        "Answer":"3.9 billion dollars",
        "Level":"6"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what is the total financial liabilities at fair value of Goldman Sachs in 2012?",
        "Answer":"377677 million dollars",
        "Level":"6"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what was brazilian paper sales of International Paper Company in 2006?",
        "Answer":"496 million dollars",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what was brazilian paper sales of International Paper Company in 2005?",
        "Answer":"465 million dollars",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what is the cashflow of Kellogg in 2006?",
        "Answer":"957.4 million dollars",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"From the perspective of 6 years ago, what percentage of total minimum lease payments of Dish Network are due in 2015?",
        "Answer":"9.772%",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"in 2011 what was the SL Green Realty Corp's percent of the change in the account balance at end of year",
        "Answer":"6.75%",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what was the value in thousands of unvested restricted stock and performance awards at the weighted-averagegrant-datefair value as of december 31 , 2018 of Global Payments?",
        "Answer":"117624.84",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"based on the cash dividends paid of the year, how many common stock shares were outstanding in 2007 Snap-on?",
        "Answer":"58909091",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what is the Entergy Corp's 2008 total value , in millions of dollars , of issuable long-term securities?",
        "Answer":"1450",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"for the capital framework of Goldman Sachs Group 8 years ago, what percent of the minimum supplementary leverage ratio consisted of a buffer?",
        "Answer":"40%",
        "Level":"6"
    },
    {
        "Question":"in 2007 what was the 3M's ratio of the interest expense to the interest income",
        "Answer":"1.59",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what is the AON's decrease observed in the additions for tax positions of prior years as of 2018, in millions?",
        "Answer":"2",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"In 2014 Global Payments, what is the total value of securities approved by security holders but net yer issued , ( in millions ) ?",
        "Answer":"365.4",
        "Level":"4"
    },
    {
        "Question":"what is the percent of our network route miles that is owned rather than operated on pursuant to trackage rights or leases in 2016 Union Pacific Corp",
        "Answer":"81.2%",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the American Tower Corp's current ratio in 13 years ago?",
        "Answer":1.7923,
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the DISH Network Corporation's current ratio in 14 years ago?",
        "Answer":1.7804,
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the American Tower Corp's current ratio in 2012?",
        "Answer":1.7923,
        "Level":"1"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the DISH Network Corporation's current ratio in 2011?",
        "Answer":1.7804,
        "Level":"1"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the International Paper Company's Operating Profit Margin of printing papers business in 2006?",
        "Answer":9.769119769,
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the International Paper Company's Operating Profit Margin of printing papers business in 2005?",
        "Answer":6.59693166,
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the International Paper Company's Operating Profit Margin of printing papers business in 2004?",
        "Answer":7.119831815,
        "Level":"6"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the Air Products and Chemicals' Operating Profit Margin in 2016?",
        "Answer":26.7735375,
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the Air Products and Chemicals' Operating Profit Margin in 2015?",
        "Answer":21.88472888,
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the Air Products and Chemicals' Operating Profit Margin in 2014?",
        "Answer":18.69805075,
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the difference of Operating Profit Margin between Air Products and Chemicals in 2016 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2006?",
        "Answer":"17.00441774",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the average of Operating Profit Margin between Air Products and Chemicals in 2016 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2005?",
        "Answer":"16.68523458",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the sum of Operating Profit Margin between Air Products and Chemicals in 2016 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2004?",
        "Answer":"33.89336932",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which one's Operating Profit Margin is bigger between Air Products and Chemicals in 2014 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2006?",
        "Answer":"Air Products and Chemicals",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the difference of Operating Profit Margin between Air Products and Chemicals in 2015 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2006?",
        "Answer":"12.11560911",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the average of Operating Profit Margin between Air Products and Chemicals in 2015 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2005?",
        "Answer":"14.24083027",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the sum of Operating Profit Margin between Air Products and Chemicals in 2015 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2004?",
        "Answer":"29.00456069",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which one's current ratio is bigger between American Tower Corp in 2012 and DISH Network Corporation in 2011?",
        "Answer":"American Tower Corp",
        "Level":"2"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the average of current ratio between American Tower Corp in 2012 and DISH Network Corporation in 2011?",
        "Answer":"1.786341177",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the difference of current ratio between American Tower Corp in 2012 and DISH Network Corporation in a year before that?",
        "Answer":"0.01185521735",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the Goldman Sachs Group's Total Assets change from 2014 to 2016 multiplied by the average of current ratio between American Tower Corp in 2012 and DISH Network Corporation in 2011?",
        "Answer":"48722.45 million",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the Goldman Sachs Group's Total Assets change from 2013 to 2017 multiplied by the average of current ratio between American Tower Corp in 2012 and DISH Network Corporation in 2011?",
        "Answer":"46296.6 million",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the sum of Goldman Sachs Group's Total Assets from 2011 to 2014 divided by the average of Operating Profit Margin between Air Products and Chemicals in 2016 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2005?",
        "Answer":"217529.28 million",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the sum of Goldman Sachs Group's Total Assets from 2011 to 2014 multiplied by the average of Operating Profit Margin between Air Products and Chemicals in 2015 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2005?",
        "Answer":"51687477.96 million",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the Goldman Sachs Group's Total Assets change from 2014 to 2016 divided the difference of Operating Profit Margin between Air Products and Chemicals in 2016 and printing papers business of International Paper Company in 2006?",
        "Answer":"1604 million",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the difference in total assets for the financial sector company founded in the 1869 between 2013 and 2017?",
        "Answer":"25917 million",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the difference in revenue for the oldest transportation sector S&P500 company between 2013 and 2016?",
        "Answer":"2022 million",
        "Level":"3"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the Operating Profit Margin in 2015 for the process industries sector company founded in 1940s and headquartered in Pennsylvania?",
        "Answer":21.88472888,
        "Level":"6"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What was the current ratio in 2012 for the financial sector company with a P\/E ratio between 40 and 50 and a market cap exceeding 100 billion dollars now?",
        "Answer":1.7923,
        "Level":"4"
    },
    {
        "Question":"What is the Operating Profit Margin in 2005 for the printing papers business of the process industries sector company founded in 1890s and headquartered in Tennessee?",
        "Answer":6.59693166,
        "Level":"2"
    }
]